Anaheim attempting to keep it deep broken
up by William Karlsson.
He springs a man Mitch Marner who's in and
he stops it home!
Mitchell Marner! It's a stretch pass from
Wild Bill.
William Karlsson put it right on the money
in game six.
Vegas off and running. There's Mitch
Marner.
Look at the end of this goal. No, not
here, right there.
What a beautiful play there by Karlsson to
recognize he's got a second.
Gets his head up, sees Marner streaking
right down the middle.
And what a skilled play there by Marner.
Between the legs and tucks it by.
No stall for the early lead. And then
Mitch Marner, look how low he is on that
puck.
Uses his body to defend Lacombe and just
stays with it.
I mean that's an almost unstoppable goal
here.
As he pulls it to the back end, he's
almost at the far post.
And look at that, he tucks it right
between the legs, snips between the legs
and just
opened that there. What a skilled play by
Marner.
But it all started with that pass from
Karlsson.
Mitch Marner, his seventh goal of the
postseason.
He has 17 points leading all scorers.
Turns out Mitch Marner is pretty good at
this playoff hockey thing.
Not bad. Yeah, a minute into the
elimination game, buries what is easily
the goal of
the postseason. I mean what else is there
to say?
The guy's unbelievable. He's got to win
the Conn Smythe.
He's such a smart, intelligent player.
And it's obvious and he's exposing a lot
of the defenses.
Does your body just take over or is that a
move that you see opening up in that
particular
space? I don't know. I think it's honestly
just kind of just a feel thing there at
that
moment. You know, I knew I had Lacombe
kind of on my back there and just tried to
kind
of go to my backhand there and see if I
had an option.
And Dostal kind of had me covered there.
So just quickly tried to pull it back
between my legs.
And tuck it in and tuck it in if it worked
out.
That and one mix tape. Oh, house house.
♪ Come on. Stringer race. Bone collector.
♪
♪ Mitchy Mitchy Mitchy. Can't you see? ♪
♪ Sometimes your moves just hypnotize me.
♪
♪ Bad boy. ♪